Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum H
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Programs and Colleges, 1977-2006; Series II
  - United Board Visiting Scholars program
    - Korea
      - Cho, Dr. Woo Hyun, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 305)
        Including regarding: Soong Si University
      - Ha, Dr. Joe Eun, 1987-1990 (Box 33, Folder 306)
        Including regarding: Yongsei University
      - Moon, Dr. Mrs. Mi-Sun, 1994-1998, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 307)
        Including regarding: Seoul Women's University
      - Park, Dr. Mr. Eun-Koo (Box 34, Folder 308)
    - Philippines
      - Baskinas, Ms. Maria Concepcion (Box 34, Folder 309)
        Including regarding: St. Scholastica's College
      - De la Cruz, Ms. Jocelyn, 1992-1995, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 310)
        Including regarding: Trinity College of Quezon City
      - Futalan, Ms. Gloria, 1995-1997 (Box 34, Folder 311)
        Including regarding: Silliman University
      - Pareja, Ms. Lynn J., 1994-1996 (Box 34, Folder 312)
        Including regarding: Central Philippine University
      - Romarate, Ms. Carla Gay, 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 313)
      - Suyo, Ms. Perla, 1993-1996 (Box 34, Folder 314)
      - Tan, Dr. Betsy Joy (Box 34, Folder 315)
    - Thailand
      - Wattanakul, Dr. Mrs. Perla (Box 34, Folder 316)
        Including regarding: Payap University
    - Vietnam
      - To, Ms. Thanh, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 317)
        Including regarding: Vietnam National University
      - To, Ms. Thanh (Box 34, Folder 318)
    - Misc.
      - Various (Box 34, Folder 319)
        Including regarding: Various scholars
- Faculty Development Program, 1980-1995; Series III
  - Application forms
    - UBCHEA China Program, 1981-1985 (Box 35, Folder 320-326)
      Including forms, worksheets
    - UBCHEA China Program, 1985-1988 (Box 36, Folder 327-333)
    - UBCHEA China Program, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 334-340)
    - UBCHEA China Program, 1991-1993 (Box 38, Folder 341-346)
  - Summary Sheets
    - UBCHEA China Program, 1980-1984 (Box 39, Folder 347)
    - UBCHEA China Program, 1980-1992 (Box OV-1)
      Including regarding: Forms, worksheets
    - UBCHEA China Program, 1982-1993 (Box 39, Folder 348-352)
    - Summary Sheets, 1994-1995 (Box 40, Folder 353)
    - Summary Sheets, 1988-1992 (Box 40, Folder 354)
      Including regarding: Support for Institutions in China
    - Summary Sheets (Box 40, Folder 355)
      Including regarding: UBCHEA Institutional giving analysis
    - Summary Sheets, 1984-1987 (Box 40, Folder 356)
      Including regarding: Scholar return
    - Summary Sheets, 1983-1991 (Box 40, Folder 357-358)
      Including regarding: Mellon Professors
    - Summary Sheets (Box 40, Folder 359)
      Including regarding: China Studies Program
- Collected Material, Series IV
  - Photos and video
    - "Home Away from Home", 2000 (Box 41, Folder 360)
      Including regarding: Video cassette
    - Photographs, 2000, 2003, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 361)
      Including regarding: United Board Scholars Conference, Ethical Quest in Higher Education: Opportunities and Challenges: Asian Christian Faculty Fellowship-II: Madras Christian College
  - Publications
    - "An International Symposium on 'Religions, Morality and Social Concern'" (Box 41, Folder 362)
      Including regarding: Writing edited by Wang Xinsheng
    - Women's Studies in Asia (Box 41, Folder 363)
      Including regarding: Written by Betty C. Abregana
  - University Conference
    - Fu Jen University, 1990 Sep 28- Oct 1 (Box 41, Folder 364-367)
      Including regarding: Conference materials
    - Fu Jen University, 1990 Sep 28- Oct 1 (Box 42, Folder 368-370)
  - Press
    - United Board, 1990 Sep (Box 42, Folder 371)
      Including regarding: Name and address list